(Stuart:)Where do you get off sending me
to shop with your girlfriend?!
(Sheldon:)I don't understand.
(Sheldon:)You were happy to do this
when I hired you.
Why-why are you
upset with me now?
(Stuart:)Oh, I'm not upset with you, but
Amy's pretty bent out of shape,
(Stuart:)so she hired me
to let you have it.
(Sheldon:)Well, I suppose
turnabout is fair play.
(Stuart:)You're darn right it's fair
play, you selfish jerk!
(Amy:)You know, just when I think
(Amy:)we're making progress
in our relationship,
(Amy:)we revert to our old patterns
(Amy:)where thoughts and feelings
go unexpressed.
(Amy:)I mean, if he didn't want
to go shopping with me,
(Amy:)why didn't he just say so?
(Beverly:)Maybe he couldn't get
a word in edgewise.
(Amy:)I'm sorry, I've been
going on and on.
(Beverly:)Oh, it's all right, dear.
(Beverly:)Sheldon has a brilliant
and complicated mind.
(Beverly:)It's understandable that being
in a relationship with him
(Beverly:)could be trying.
I called him “babe” once.
(Amy:)He asked me to get a drug test.
(Beverly:)Well, I do admire your resolve.